What did you do to Kinoshita?
I kissed her. Only on the forehead though.
Don't let people like that ruin our friendship.
That's just wrong.
You're such a weirdo, Kinoshita.
Sayuri and Daiki are now officially a couple!
You can't expect anything from Ren
so long as he has a girlfriend.
You don't understand the limits there are
in your relationship with him.
I'll help you forget Ren, for good.
So try experiencing romance with me.
I'm sorry.
I can't date someone while having these feelings for Ren.
You can never be more than friends with him though.
I never expected anything more than that.
Humans are creatures of greed.
If you truly love him, you'll hope for more.
But with Ren, that sort of next step is impossible.
You'll only learn to feel oppressed by that reality.
Those are the limits I'm talking about.
- But...
- No need to give me an answer now.
I'm sure you'll face your limits soon enough.
Come to me when it becomes obvious, yeah?
I know Ren already has Mayuka.
But there's no limit to liking someone.
Morning.
This one's so cute!
You'd pull it off, Sayu.
- You think?
- Totally.
Uehara, you're on duty today.
Come grab the notebooks from the teacher's lounge.
But I'm busy right now.
You are not. Now hurry.
- Be right back.
- See you.
- These other accessories aren't bad either.
- Yeah.
Which one was Sayuri raving about? Show me!
This one.
Didn't realize she liked hearts.
Why not get it for her as a Christmas present?
That was the plan.
You might want to take a closer look.
Huh? Forty-two...
[Price: 42,000 Yen]
Too high of a hurdle, huh?
No, I can afford this.
- Barely.
- Seriously?
Messing around with the Director again?
Ren.
That's still his position, right?
Yup.
He's still a hefty director.
- Could I hold him?
- Go ahead.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to...
Don't sweat it. That was an accident.
I'm going to grab some more trash bags.
But she pushed me away. That stings.
I think I'm coming to despise you for real this time, Ren.
What the...
My heart is wavering. It hurts.
I feel like I'm choking up.
I don't know what this is.
That'll be 380 yen.
I'm starving.
[Episode 4]
I wonder if they'll still have the Cheese-Pickled Plum Rolls.
Is that even on the menu?
It is.
Look, it's Ren.
You don't need to hide.
Sometimes a girl needs to hide from her crush.
You pervert!
What's up, Ninako?
Nothing!
Ren seems off, doesn't he?
38.7 degrees?
Didn't realize it was that bad.
Go lie down and rest.
- Could you help him up?
- Of course.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You should speak up when you're not feeling well.
Trying to push through never makes it easier.
Head home once you rest up, alright?
- Slap that cooling patch on him.
- Right.
I'll be fine once I lie down for a bit.
I have a part-time shift today anyway.
Are you crazy?
I'll cover your shift, so get some rest at home.
You don't have to always try so hard, you know?
I guess so.
- See you.
- Thanks again.
- Take care.
- You too.
I'm absolutely beat.
- Thankfully it wasn't a busy day.
- Yeah.
I'm glad it's not just me and Ando.
It's so cold today.
Ando, could I grab that scarf from you?
And leave me to freeze? No can do.
Stingy.
Well, I'm headed this way.
- See you two.
- See you.
Don't let my confession bother you.
As if.
I want it to weigh on your mind.
But not to the point of troubling you.
And since it seems like this is awkward for you,
I'll head home by a different way.
Careful on your way back.
Yeah, thanks.
Here, take this.
What? It's fine, I'll manage.
Besides, didn't you say you'd freeze?
I'm only nice to girls I like.
I'm not kind to just anyone, okay?
See you, for real this time.
Kinoshita.
- Morning.
Thanks for covering my shift the other day.
How are you feeling?
I feel much better.
I practically spent the entire weekend in bed.
Let me cover a shift for you to make up for it.
It's fine. With exam season coming up,
I've only scheduled one shift a week anyway.
Then is there anything else I can do for you?
Sorry, I can't think of anything.
My brain is fried from cramming and sleep deprivation.
Your explanation makes much more sense this week.
I should've expected nothing less from the Math God.
Stop it with that nickname.
Ren, do you like math?
I love it.
Didn't we have this conversation already?
Did we? Sorry, my bad.
Sorry.
Now arriving at Shin-Sakuta.
The doors on the left side will open.
"I wonder how she'll react
when I give her my Christmas present?"
So? Did I read your mind?
What? Did not.
Hey guys, thanks for waiting.
- Dad, you're so late.
- Sorry.
[Yohei Korenaga]
- Thank you.
- Your menus.
Much appreciated.
Aren't you busy studying for college entrance exams, Mayuka?
Yeah, but I could make time.
I bet she's more busy with work and romance.
Hey, I find time to study.
Are things going well with your boyfriend?
Yup.
What about you, Dad?
Thinking of getting back together with Mom?
I guess not.
I wanted to talk about something related to that.
Sorry! Was I leaning on you the entire time?
The next stop is Nijinodai.
We passed your stop.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay, I passed out too.
Liar. I know you.
You just felt bad about poking me awake.
- I'm so sorry.
- I was asleep, really.
You don't need to apologize.
Alright, see you tomorrow.
What? I'll wait for your train with you.
It's really the least I could do.
You shouldn't stay out any later than you need to.
- But...
- No buts.
It's already late as it is.
Okay, fine. Then I'll get going.
Yeah. See you.
Ren!
I'd better keep you company while you wait.
Close call.
Why?
Why are you like this?
Sorry, I can't help it.
It's getting late. You really should head home for the day.
Okay.
Humans are creatures of greed.
If you truly love him, you'll hope for more.
You can't expect anything from Ren
so long as he has a girlfriend.
You don't understand the limits there are
in your relationship with him.
You're wrong.
It's not like that.
With Ren, that sort of next step is impossible.
I know that already.
[Mayuka Korenaga]
[Melting Lip Color]
- Nice color, right?
- Yeah.
- See you.
- See you around.
What's up? It's already pretty late today.
Sayuri, I'm sorry.
For what?
My dad's job is transferring him to Fukuoka.
He's moving there with his new wife,
and I'm going with them.
I tried telling him I wanted to stay here
with my sister and our mom.
But I couldn't.
Because my dad, he was smiling.
He looked so sad to leave us.
I couldn't raise any objections.
I decided I would go with him of my own accord.
But I don't want to leave you either.
I just don't know anymore...
Maybe we should elope.
Sure.
Huh?
Let's go.
Let's get a bit closer.
Come on!
I only hear the waves.
It's like we're alone in the world.
Yeah.
I'll go buy something warm to drink.
Be right back.
Thanks.
You didn't get anything for yourself?
I'll be fine.
Let's share this then.
That hits the spot.
- Here.
- Thanks.
We'll have to start pinching pennies.
We'll drop out, rent a cheap apartment,
and we'll start working.
What sort of job should I start with?
Maybe I should work part-time at a cafe, like Ninako.
Working at a bakery sounds nice, too.
Didn't you say you wanted to become a nail technician?
Yeah.
But that requires attending a beauty school,
and getting a license.
It's fine.
I wasn't serious about becoming one anyway.
I'm sorry for making you lie.
I'm sorry I'm forcing you to entertain my whims.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
I'll get a part-time job.
I'll save up, so I can visit you often.
We'll make this work, won't we?
I'm the one who decided I would go along with my dad.
I don't want you to have to accommodate me.
If I had it my way, this would be a Christmas present.
In that case...
Give it to me, on Christmas.
I'm sorry.
This is good bye, Sayuri.
"AX-squared plus AX plus C equals..."
Hey, no studying during lunch break.
Sorry, but I refuse to fail math again.
- I'm taking that.
- Hey!
Thief...
I wonder if Sayuri and Daiki are okay.
They haven't come in today.
I'll try giving them a call.
What?
I heard about your dad's transfer.
And about what happened with Sayu, too.
I seriously thought for a second
that the two of us could elope.
Damn, I'm such a kid.
And you're fine with this, Daiki?
Don't you love Sayu?
Of course I love her.
That's why I have to do this. For Sayuri.
- Ouch.
- What are you trying to act all mature for?
You aren't thinking about what's best for Sayu at all.
Sayu doesn't want you to become "mature" for her sake.
What would you know?
More than you, apparently.
You know what Sayu told me?
She said she loves how honest and devoted you are.
So go be straightforward,
and fumble around like you always do.
I'm going to go speak to Sayuri again.
Good.
Ninako.
My sister, she...
She's also going through a rough time.
She's probably taking the news worse than I am.
So, what I'm trying to say is...
I know. Mayuka needs Ren right now.
I guess it's true.
No feelings last forever, do they?
Ren.
It's okay.
I won't leave you.
I'll always be here for you.
I have to shut these feelings up inside me.
I can't ever expect anything more.
Christmas is coming up.
I confessed to Ninako.
I'll prove to you some things won't ever change.
Even if I kept piling on reasons to love him,
it would only hurt in the end.
I don't care if you think you'll look lame.
Just tell me how you really feel.
Can we talk?
[Epilogue]
Morning. How are you feeling?
Sometimes I feel like crying,
even though I'm not sad.
But...
This only happens when I'm with Kinoshita.
It's like I'm me, but I'm not myself.
Nothing wrong with finding a new side to yourself.
But I think this is wrong.
Something tells me it is.